Guide to the Greentree Stud and Stable Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Materials, 1926-2000; Accession 2011-M-064
  - Topical
    - Miscellaneous--"Anything Goes" lyrics (mentions stable), Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Saratoga Springs
      - Betsey Cushing Whitney estate, appraisal report, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Greentree Stable sales brochure, Circa 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Main house and other structures, insurance, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Realtor brochures and correspondence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
      - Indenture deeding property to Betsey Cushing Whitney, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Easement from Betsey Cushing Whitney to the Corporation of Yaddo, Inc., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Property description of easement from Betsey Cushing Whitney to the Corporation of Yaddo, Inc., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Yaddo, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Betsey Cushing Whitney estate administration correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5-7)
      - Betsey Cushing Whitney estate sale of property, primarily on Nelson Avenue to Stonerside Stable, 1999 October 8 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Greentree Stud (Lexington, Kentucky) sale
      - Correspondence, 1988 May 1-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
      - Broker agreement, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
      - Escrow materials, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Special warranty deed, 1989 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Foreign Investment in Real Property Tax Act (FIRPTA) affidavit, 1989 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Notices of termination
        - Management agreement, 1989 August 18 (Box 9, Folder 8)
        - Employees, 1989 August 18 (Box 9, Folder 9)
        - Service contracts, 1989 August 15 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Letter of agreement, 1989 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Maintenance and payroll, 1988 September 1- 1989 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
      - Renwick Kentucky, Ltd. (RKL)
        - Certificate of incorporation, 1988 December 20 (Box 9, Folder 14)
        - Bylaws, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        - Certified resolutions, 1989 August 4 (Box 9, Folder 16)
        - Incumbency certificate, 1989 August (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Offers of employment to employees, 1989 August 17 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Title documentation, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Index of documents, 1989 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Title company affidavits, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Invoice for survey, 1989 August 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Wiring instructions, 1989 August 30 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Letter of agreement regarding apportionments, 1989 August 31 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Closing (checks and receipts), 1989 August 31 (Box 10, Folder 4-7)
      - Power of attorney (Betsey Cushing Whitney to W. Scott Blanchard), 1989 August 29-31 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
      - Sale of equipment, 1989 August 31 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Service contracts, 1989 July (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Apportionment schedules, 1989 August (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - List of employees, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Labor proceedings, 1989 July (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Deeds, 1926-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Memoranda, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Document index and closing checklist, 1989 August 30 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Structural of meeting of Board of Directors, 1982 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Structural of closing documents (Betsey Cushing Whitney to Renwick Kentucky, Ltd.), 1989 August 31 (Box 10, Folder 19-22)
    - Greentree Stable (Aiken, South Carolina) sale
      - Correspondence, 1990 February 22-1991 January 16 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
      - Closing documents index, 1999 February 22 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Deeds conveying portions of the property, 1976-1978, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Property description, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Appraisal, 1990 February 12-20 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Brokerage agreement, 1990 March 5 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Letter of intent, 1990 July 6 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Contract of sale, 1990 September 6 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Escrow agreement, 1990 September 6 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Down payment, 1990 August 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Limited warranty deed, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Bill of sale, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Note, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Mortgage, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Foreign Investment in Real Property Tax Act (FIRPTA) affidavit, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Gains tax affidavits and returns, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
      - Disbursement letter, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Taxes, letter regarding, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Title insurance policy, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Survey, 1990 July 30 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Seller's insurance policies, 1990 September 13 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Reinacher, Robert J., Jr., letter, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Instructions regarding down payment, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Meter readings and county taxes, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Apportionment schedule, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Broker's letter, 1990 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Broker's commission, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
      - Power of attorney, 1990 Jul, September (Box 11, Folder 32-33)
      - Payoff documents, 1990 September 14-1991 January 9 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Notes, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Shearman & Sterling memoranda regarding sale, 1990 July 27-December 13 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Ends Well participation dispute
      - Memoranda and notes, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
      - Research, 1968-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)